wbadmin 1.0 - Backup command-line tool
(C) Copyright 2012 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.

The scheduled backup settings:

Bare metal recovery : Not Included
System state backup: Not Included
Volumes in backup: (C:)
Components in backup: (null)
Files excluded: None
Advanced settings: VSS Backup Option (COPY)
Location to store backup: F:
Times of day to run backup: 09:00

